filesbomb.com 2014-11-21

# Filesbomb.com - Privacy

__**Privacy Policy:**__

  * With Every upload process the following Data is gathered and stored in our log files and servers  

A- User name that uploaded the file. 

B- The date and the time in which the file was uploaded.

c- The IP ( internet protocol) of the user who uploaded the file.

_      **  _Other Technical info that is gathered during your upload or download process:_**_

  * Our log files store some technical data of our visitors whether for statistics purposes or for enhancing our visitors experience to filesbomb.com, this data includes but not limit to IP address, type of browser, type of OS, referrer website, referrer search engine...etc. 

  * Cookies maybe used to recall the visitor during future visits.

  * A user e-mail and user name will be stored during registration.

  * e-mail addresses will NOT be sold or rented in anyway at any circumstances.

  * filesbomb team might send e-mail to it's members for upgrades and news.   
 filesbomb.com

        __**Google Adsense policy:**__

  We use Google ad sense to serve ads in filesbomb.com.

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on filesbomb.com.

  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our visitors based on their visit to filesbomb and/or other sites on the Internet.

  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

  __**DMCA Policy**__

filesbomb (filesbomb.com) is an Online Service Provider under Title II of the Digital Millennium Copyright Act, 17 U.S.C. Section 512 ("DMCA"). This document outlines the policy that filesbomb.com has introduced in order to implement notice and takedown policy as required by DMCA. This document guides copyright owners interested in utilizing this procedure, as well as service users interested in restoring access to material mistakenly taken down.   
Writing and sending Proper Notification

The DMCA provides a legal procedure by which you can request any Online Service Provider to disable access to a website where your copyrighted work(s) are appearing without your permission. The legal procedure consists of two parts: (1) Writing a Proper DMCA Notice, and (2) Sending the Proper DMCA Notice to filesbomb.com Designated Agent.  
To write a Proper DMCA Notice, state the following information:

  *   
Identify yourself as an owner of copyrighted work or exclusive rights that you believe were infringed, or a person acting on behalf of such owner.

  *   
State your contact information, including your name, street address, phone number, and email address.  
Identify the copyrighted work that you believe is being infringed, or if a large number of works are being infringed, a representative list of the works.

  *   
Identify the location of materials that allegedly are infringing your copyrighted work, by providing Web URLs on filesbomb.com site that contain these materials. Please don't send attached images, pdf or other file formats files, but only list with filesbomb.com web urls.

  *   
State that you have "a good faith belief that use of the aforementioned material is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agents, or the law".

  *   
State that the information in the notice is accurate, under penalty of perjury. 

  *   
Your notice must be signed with a physical signature (when it is in paper form) or electronic signature (when it is in electronic form).

  *   
To exercise your DMCA rights, your Proper DMCA Notice must be sent to Designated Agent of filesbomb.com to email: [admin@filesbomb.com](mailto:admin@filesbomb.com)

_**Notice and takedown procedures**_   
filesbomb.com will follow the procedures provided in the DCMA to properly enforce rights of copyright holders. When a Proper DMCA notification is received by Designated Agent, or when filesbomb.com becomes otherwise aware that copyright rights are infringed, it will remove or disable access to infringing materials in 24 to 48 hours. You don't need to wait confirmation from us about this action.

## **Privacy Policy for www.filesbomb.com**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at support@filesbomb.com. 

At www.filesbomb.com , the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.filesbomb.com and how it is used. 

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.filesbomb.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.filesbomb.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.filesbomb.com .  
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to www.filesbomb.com and other sites on the Internet.   
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. 

Our **advertising partners include .......**  
**Google Adsense**

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.filesbomb.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

www.filesbomb.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.filesbomb.com 's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
